Hi!
I would like to invite you to visit our website at www.teamclarke.org.
A good parka is something to have and with that good parka you want to have a really good rough.
They make ruffs out of different animal hides.
The ruff is sort of that piece that goes around the top of the hood and a ruff will gather close to your face and keep the frost bite off your cheeks and nose.
If it is made out of the correct animal hide, coyote is used by sort of mid-priced parkas.
This is a really good parka and Linda bought me; this is a Wolverine Double Ruff; wolf on the outside and wolverine closest to your skin.
The 2 vest pieces of fur to keep frost off your face.
Neither wolf nor wolverine will absorb water or frost which is why they are used versus some of the other ruff materials.
Ruff’s have been made out of coyote.
I’ve got one here made out of coyote ruff.
Wolf is pretty prevalent; wolverine is getting pricier, very little trapping of wolverine in this state, so we usually get it from Northern Canada.
Then I have a 2 parka system where I would wear an anorak which is a pull over type of garment that doesn’t zip all the way down.
That keeps the wind from getting in the holes created naturally by the zipper.